I look up to the stars and reach for
the sky I believe in tomorrow if we try!
Hey!
Come on, let's go, everybody!
Oh, we share the music!
We share the music!
Come on, let's go, baby, baby!
Oh, we share the one dream!
Come on, let's go, everybody!
Oh, we share the good times!
We share the good times!
Let's go, baby, baby, oh,
we share the one world.
It's hard to see for you and me.
Through the darkness
that is in this world.
So hard to see, but to believe.
In where we need to go.
Yes, you and me, it's true that we.
Feel the rush brought on by this world.
Through head to feet, I feel the beat.
Getting me to walk on, oh yeah.
Share the music, no matter what.
Share the one dream, believe in yourself.
Share the good times, take my hand now.
Share the one world now.
I look up to the stars.
And reach for the sky.
No matter what.
I'll try no matter how high.
So let us go.
Beyond, far and wide.
I believe in tomorrow.
If we try high.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come on, let's go, everybody.
Oh, we share the music.
Come on, let's go, baby, baby.
Oh, we share the one world.
Oh, as we chase, we're being chased.
From the top we go, one straight and wild.
We're on our way, I've got to say.
Hey, I want to share your style.
Now here it starts, so don't lose heart.
They're bound to lose to this flavor.
From boot to hood, I feel so good.
I will be free to be, oh yeah.
Share the music, even if I.
Share the one dream, I know where you are.
Share the good times, show us that smile.
Share the one world now.
I look up to the stars.
And reach for the sky.
No matter what.
I'll try no matter how high.
So let us go, beyond, far and wide.
I believe in tomorrow if we try.
I know that you are there,
just on the other side.
Wait there for me, soon
it will be you and I.
Then let us go, beyond, far and wide.
I believe in the one world if we try.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come on, let's go, everybody,
oh, we share the music, hey, hey.
Come on, let's go, baby, baby,
oh, we share the one world.
Huh?
The Dark King Silver's Rayleigh, huh?
Somehow nobody recognized him,
so they're about to sell
him off at an auction
like they would any other normal old man.
They're selling the Dark King as a slave?
It does seem far-fetched
to be honest my men
aren't even entirely
certain it's actually him.
Teeth yes sir so how
should we handle this vice
admiral should I report
it to fleet admiral?
Sengoku no i intend to handle this myself
don't tell anyone about
this not even sengoku
and make sure your men
keep their mouths shut
but sir what if it
really is the dark king?
oh it's him all right there's
no doubt about it huh this
isn't the first sighting of
him on the islands that's
been reported he's probably
racked up some gambling
debt and sold himself in
order to pay it off Rayleigh
may be an old man but if we
don't approach him carefully
the military will lose an
unthinkable number of men
the timing couldn't be worse
you really think the navy
has the manpower to take on
two legends at the same time?
all
right
ladies
and gentlemen
thank you for joining us
the moment you've been waiting
for has finally arrived
the monthly great human
auction of grove number one is
about to begin and here comes
everyone's favorite emcee?
Here he is, the walking super
bazaar himself, Mr. Disco!
Thank you, everyone.
As always, we've collected the finest
lineup of slaves for your wants and needs.
And you are in luck.
We've got an extra special
item for sale today.
I pray from the bottom of
my heart that each and every
one of you will leave with
the slave of your choice.
but enough talk let's get this auction
going you heard the man get two and three
ready to go yeah i'm on it item number
one hails from torah in the west blue
he's a proud pirate from a long line
of musicians and what a talent hand him
any instrument you like name a song and
just watch him go he's a living breathing
jukebox for your home a jukebox that'll
mop up any unsightly mess you spill it
he'll clean it up and he's an expert
winemaker he's a 25 year old human in his
prime just look six foot four 286 pounds
going by the name of Byron we'll start
the bidding at 480,000 berries all right
let's see those paddles and hear your bids
number seven is opening it up with our
starting price do we have another bid
Sold for 600,000 berries
What a sick joke Devil, is
this list what I think it is?
Yes, market prices This is insane
Standard starting price
for a human is 500,000
berries Male giants start
at 50 million Holy crap!
Female mermaids are
worth 70 million berries?
That's why everyone goes after mermaids.
It's their get-rich-quick scheme.
That's a lot of berries.
Naturally, once they get bought, they
lose every ounce of their freedom.
They usually wind up as decorations
for some rich snob living
out their lives in cramped
fish tanks as exotic eye candy.
Why the hell are you even telling me this?
Well, I say living, but you really
can't call it that, can you?
If that's how you feel,
hurry up and find her!
We've done a thorough search of all the
kidnapping rings in grove number 20, sir!
Make this thing go faster!
Will you get off my ass, kid?
She ain't a bird!
She needs a running start to get going!
Kuma!
Where are you?
It pisses me off.
Jeez, it was a damn giant.
How often did you find a giant sleeping?
It was the easiest catch of my life, but
it was still a pain hauling the thing here.
A giant like that would normally be the
main attraction and we'd
all be billionaires,
but no.
Some jerk's got to go
and bring a mermaid in
at the last minute before
the auction starts.
I need a drink.
Hey, hold on.
Now, who brought in the mermaid?
This is fish number five.
Here, attention all rosy life riders!
Come in, riders.
We've got an idea on the kidnapper.
It was Peterman.
Word is he sold the mermaid to the
auction house on growth number one.
Wait!
It was Peterman!
Do you know where to go?
Yes, I do.
Must be flying so fast!
I just hope she hasn't
been sold off already.
Hurry up!
Grove number one is right around
the corner, just leave it to me!
We're headed for the auction house!
You, you mean we know where she is?
Thank goodness!
Kuma!
And a move on!
I'm trying to get back to my ship.
Fellas know where grove number one is?
Heh, well sure we do!
Really?
Mind telling me?
Up next, entry number six
for your consideration.
A ten-pack of stout and
sturdy male human laborers.
Calling all units.
Head to grove number one, and someone
read off the auction schedule.
It started at four.
It's been going for 30 minutes now.
Are we going to make it in time?
Oh, we'll make it.
A mermaid's always considered
a big-ticket attraction,
so they won't auction her
off until the second half.
Nothing to worry about.
Just take the fastest route you can.
You're a lot slower than the flying fish.
Sure, you just sit back and take
it easy there, young master.
There's a reason why I'm the
boss of this team, you know.
Did you notice me change direction back
when we found out where the mermaid was?
Uh, no, I didn't.
And that's because...
I've been steering us toward Grove No.
1 since the very beginning.
Just look, that's the auction house.
The boss is always going to be
the first to crash the party.
How the hell'd you know where to go?
Have you got some kidnapper intuition?
All right, little buddy, this is it.
Thank you, sir.
Oh, hey, it's Sanji.
First one there, my ass.
Thanks, bro.
Boo.
What's with this guy?
Two million berries.
Any other bids?
This is it.
What the hell do you mean
you can't give her back?
Huh?
I don't care how things work here.
You have no right to sell Kuma.
You're the one who's in
the wrong here, friend.
Keep harassing us and we'll
have to sue you for...
obstruction of business.
This is crap.
Business my ass, you heartless turd.
This isn't a business.
You're just profiting off
the misery of the week.
A lawless pirate like you has no
right to lecture me on morality.
Slavery is considered
taboo the whole world over.
How much are you paying the
government to get away with this?
That's not a very nice thing to say,
but you're not too far off base.
I admit that whenever the
government or the Navy stops by,
they have a very difficult time
hearing the words human trafficking.
Why, I get the impression they don't have
a clue that we're selling anyone at all.
What a load of crap.
We know you're in this together.
What the heck is the government
thinking letting this fly?
Who cares that they look the other way?
You should be ashamed of yourself.
Please don't make me
tell you a third time.
I've heard enough.
If we know the mermaid's
here, we're wasting time.
Ew!
You can't do that.
There are celestial
dragons in there, remember?
And if they got Kuma, you know they
put one of those colors on her by now.
You mean the ones that explode?
I guess we can't take
her out by force, then.
You're all welcome to leave now.
You're welcome to choke on my foot.
Stop, Sanji. Calm down. We can't.
Quit holding me back.
Just let it go. Damn it.
You know this creep deserves it.
Hey, Nami, where are you running off to?
You've got to calm down.
If we can't beat them with our
fists then we're just gonna have to
beat these bastards at their own
game go ahead and prepare number
15 and number 16
you got it please
don't I can't handle this
please don't make me be a slave
I'll
go
Already will you call the Navy?
I'll go to jail.
Please don't tell me to someone
Hey boss, isn't that the straw
hat crew that just walked in?
Yeah, but the Straw Hat
captain ain't with him.
Shame, since I'd like to see if
that bastard's as crazy as they say.
Moving right along, we've
got entry number 14.
Up next, we've got a deal
you simply cannot turn down.
Entry 15 is an amazingly
beautiful female human.
Just feast your eyes on those curves.
She's a 20-year-old dancer named Pasha.
Just imagine waking up to the sight
of this beguiling vision every day.
Such transcendent beauty is sure to
convince you you've died and gone to heaven.
Is this what they're going to do to Kuma?
I already told you,
we're getting Kuma back.
I'm having a little trouble
seeing how in this situation.
We've got a good deal of treasure
back on the sunny, right?
It's got to be worth
at least $200 million.
And what's the starting
market price for mermaids?
Ew, that's more than enough, but
there's no way I can pay all that back.
What are you talking about, Hachi?
Are you K-Me's legal
guardian or something?
Ew, no, that's not what I meant.
Kami's our friend,
and we'll do whatever it takes to get
her back, no matter how much it costs.
Anyone got a problem with that?
Of course not!
Money's the last thing I care about!
You guys, thank you so much!
You're like the greatest
people I've ever known!
I like it when she's spicy, but I love
when Nami's sweet! Shut up! Come on!
Faster! Faster!
I'm doing what I can, kid!
Do it faster, dammit!
I'm already at Grove number two, huh?
Not much farther to go.
I wonder if the others are already there.
WE'RE GONNA SAVE YOU, Kuma!
Extra, extra!
Read all about it!
Has the world government lost their minds?
This can't be real.
If they do that...
This spells trouble with
a capital T, Captain.
Well, that answers that.
I don't get it.
What are you talking about, sir?
It finally makes sense.
I wondered why there were
so few marines stationed
on an island within spitting
distance of a navy base.
I still don't understand.
The commander of
Whitebeard's second division,
Fire Fist Ace, is to be publicly executed.
But there's no way
Whitebeard won't retaliate.
This can only result in war.
Entry number 15!
The beautiful dancer Pasha!
It's incredible!
Her starting price of 800,000 berries has
skyrocketed to the winning
bid of 7.2 million berries!
I finally arrived it's about time but
things are really starting to get fired
up so let's keep the show moving feast
your eyes on the next piece of merchandise
what a relief sounds like it's still
going well that may be true sir I
believe I just heard him say they were
on entry number 15 which would mean the
auction is almost over because this
over slow getting yet
put this
one up for
sale I don't need it anymore I'll make
the arrangements at once hmm celestial
dragon another one huh lots of nobility
here and a navy admiral will come running
to the rescue if we defy one of them
what I really want to buy is a Mermaid?
I do hope they have one this time.
Merfolk are a notoriously
difficult species to capture,
so I fear you may leave
here disappointed yet again.
Mew.
Wait, Charles, what a surprise.
Yes, I'm sure it is.
Just take me to my seat.
Of course, right away.
I see my brother's here.
Well, better late than never.
Now let's resume shall we I present to
you entry number 16 oh my the captain of
a pirate ship with a bounty of 17 million
berries it's captain la cuba he's an
insightful strategist but don't let that
fool you he's in great physical shape as
well you can use him as a guide or as a
horse as manual labor or as a punching bag
the possibilities are endless.
Now then, let's begin.
Did he just... Oh, no.
He passed out.
What's going on down there?
I think I saw blood.
Shut the curtains.
Hurry.
What happened I couldn't
tell he bit off his tongue
he decided he'd rather die
than live with someone's
pet he saw no other way
out than to take his own
life in this case that
could be the smart choice
where's the mermaid already
amy must be so scared
this is awful just hang
on a little longer no
matter what happens we
will save her it's a good
thing we've got all that
treasure from Thriller Bark.
Thank you all so much for everything.
No good. Sorry, sir. Damn it all.
Now I'm not gonna make
one berry off of you.
You idiot.
The mermaid's next, right?
Yes, sir.
Everything's all set.
She can go up at any time. Good.
Get her on stage now. Yes, sir.
It seems entry number 16,
the pirate captain LaCuba, was so
nervous to see you all that he collapsed.
from a nosebleed.
His auction will have to wait.
We apologize for any inconvenience.
But ladies and gentlemen,
the next item I have to show you
is nothing short of incredible.
This highly sought-after prize is
sure to be on everyone's wish list.
Now, bring it to the stage!
This item is far too amazing to reveal
all at once, so we'll take it in steps.
Observe the silhouette.
It could really be. Yes, it is.
I've been waiting.
Did that whet your appetite?
Well, try not to drool, folks,
because here comes the real deal.
All the way from?
Fishman Island, the mermaid came in.
It's hotching in the Straw Hats!
They must have come here to rescue me!
Koby!
They're selling her!
Do something!
I'm on it.
We'll get her back no problem.
200 million is gonna be
more than enough. Koby!
I can't believe it! A mermaid!
They're selling a mermaid!
500 million!
I bid $500 million!
It's useless.
I can't compete with that.
How could this happen?
We don't have nearly
that much What a waste of
money Did you forget the
piranhas in your aquarium?
She won't last an hour in there
It'll be fun to watch her try though.
Merfolk are the fastest swimmers
in the world, or so they say.
I can't hear anything
they're saying out there.
Pachin, please!
Rescue me!
Everyone appears to be at a loss for
words, but I'll ask just the same.
Does anyone out there have a bid
higher than 500 million berries?
Can't we do anything about this?
I mean, there's got to
be something, right?
Come on, Sanji, what's the plan, Nami?
There isn't any time left.
If we don't do something now, they'll take
her away and we'll never get her back.
This is bad.
We should have known we
couldn't compete with them.
Those creeps throw money
around like it grows on trees.
This just isn't our game.
If not, then I'll bring the
bidding straight to a close.
Now.
You!
I won't let this happen!
I'll have to help her escape
to the ocean by force!
Don't be stupid!
What about the collar?
Do you want her head to explode?
Well, then I...
I guess I'm just gonna have to
find a way to get the key, too!
And that's it. Time's up.
I did it.
This is just a taste of
what the world holds.
It's all a damn farce.
Let's go, men.
Bidding has ended, ladies and gentlemen.
Today's showcased item,
the young mermaid, Kuma,
goes to the world noble saint,
Chalas, for his bid of...
500 million!
What is that? RERY!
What the heck?
What is all that racket?
Luffy!
Don't you know how to drive?
What kind of crappy landing was that?
Give me a break!
I'm on a fish!
Fish are no good at landing!
Damn it, Luffy!
Hurry, we gotta get to Rogue One!
It's so damn important
that you have to grab
me by the neck and send
me crashing into...
What is this place? Zoro!
Hey, it's you.
Well, damn.
If it isn't Straw Hat Luffy.
Who are those goons?
And where did they come from?
Kuma!
Luffy, save me!
I've been looking for you everywhere!
Hold on, Straw Hat!
What do you think you're doing?
What's it look like?
I'm saving Kuma!
He's wearing an explosive collar!
She'll never make it out alive!
Plus, the Celestial Dragons are here!
Don't do anything, Rat!
See if I care!
Did he just call him Straw Hat?
Kuma, I'm coming!
Straw Hat, stop this!
He's a fish man!
Disgusting!
What's a fish man doing here?
It's an octopus monster.
Hold on, Kuma, I'm on my way!
Seize him at once.
Kamey's my friend and she's not for sale.
You got that.
Keep him away from the stage.
What's a fish man doing on land?
I bet he spreads diseases.
Of course he does.
Apprehend him already!
Rose, stay away.
Go back to the sea, you damn freak!
Get out of here already.
We don't want you here.
Hachi, we need to run for it.
You're the one who's in danger now.
You're telling me to let Kuma go? No way.
Why do the people here hate him so much?
It's just like Robin said before.
They discriminate against fishmen
and merfolk on these islands.
They hate every last one of them.
But why?
They're not any different from us.
I did it!
I shot it!
I took down a fish, man! Haji!
Thank goodness someone shot it.
If that awful sea beast had gotten any
closer, it would have made us all ill.
True, and it was definitely
plotting something.
Couldn't have been much,
though, even if it can walk.
It's still got a fish's brain.
Look father, I got a fish man.
I shot it and caught it all by myself.
That means I can have it for free.
It's free, it's free.
An octopus for me.
I caught a fish man by myself.
An octopus for free.
What a deal, what a deal.
Free, free, free, free, free.
Wait.
Straw Hat.
Don't do this.
It's my fault.
I'm the one who screwed up. Okay.
Please don't forget your promise.
Like I said, you can't defy the celestial
dragons even if they kill someone!
There was a time when I was a pirate.
A criminal!
This is the punishment I deserve for
doing all of those horrible things.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean for everything
to turn out like this.
I just wanted to make amends
with Nami however I could.
Even if it wasn't much, I wanted
to be helpful to you and your crew.
But I screwed that up, I guess,
just like every other time.
I wanted to do something right for
once and show Nami how sorry I am.
All my life, all I've ever
done is cause trouble.
I'm sorry.
Forgive me.
That's enough.
Stop all that annoying babbling
fish before I shut you up for good.
Oh, how dare you don't
look at me like that.
Don't!
Straw Hat, please!
You're going to get in really big trouble!
Don't do it!
Easy.
You see this?
What is that man doing? He's crazy.
Straw Hat Luffy.
He's serious.
Now you're annoying me too!